nikiomahe.com 2012-11-17

# Privacy Policy - Architecture and Design News – Nikiomahe.com - Architecture, Design News, Interior Design, House Design, Furniture, Construction Project, and Residential

[www.nikiomahe.com](http://www.nikiomahe.com/) respect your privacy and committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at http://www.nikiomahe.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this blog/site.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers, www.nikiomahe.com use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

E-mail Subscription  
A user can subscribe to this blog posts via e-mail (powered by [Feedburner](http://www.nikiomahe.com/goto/http://www.feedburner.com)), www.nikiomahe.com ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. www.nikiomahe.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitorsâ€™ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on www.nikiomahe.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

www.nikiomahe.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. www.nikiomahe.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Links  
This blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that www.nikiomahe.com do not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this blog/website.

Advertisers  
www.nikiomahe.com use outside ad companies to display ads on this blog/site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and www.nikiomahe.com do not have access to these information. www.nikiomahe.com work with the ad companies like [Google Adsense](http://www.nikiomahe.com/goto/http://www.google.com) and [Amazon](http://www.nikiomahe.com/goto/http://www.amazon.com). Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.nikiomahe.com/contact-us/)
